let questions = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning?",
      answer: "Both 0x and 0X",
      options: [
        "00",
        "0x",
        "0X",
        "Both 0x and 0X"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "In JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error?",
      answer: "Division by zero",
      options: [
        "Missing of semicolons",
        "Syntax error",
        "Division by zero",
        "Missing of Bracket"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "When there is an indefinite or an infinite value during an arithmetic computation in a program, then JavaScript prints",
      answer: "Displays “Infinity”",
      options: [
        "Prints an overflow error",
        "Prints an exception error",
        "Prints the value as such",
        "Displays “Infinity”"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",
      answer: "Dynamic variable",
      options: [
        "Dynamic variable",
        "Mutable variable",
        "Volatile variable",
        "Immutable variable"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of the following given functions of the Number Object formats a number with a different number of digits to the right of the decimal?",
      answer: "toFixed()",
      options: [
        "toPrecision()",
        "toFixed()",
        "toExponential()",
        "toLocaleString()"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following function of the String object returns the character in the string starting at the specified position via the specified number of characters?",
      answer: "substr()",
      options: [
        "split()",
        "slice()",
        "substr()",
        "search()"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?",
      answer: "Function/Method",
      options: [
        "Triggering Event",
        "Preprocessor",
        "Function/Method",
        "RMI"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
      answer: "valueOf()",
      options: [
        "valueOf()",
        "toString()",
        "toLocaleString()",
        "DtoPrecision()"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that",
      answer: "Both are equal in the value and data type",
      options: [
        "Both are equal in the value and data type",
        "Both are not same at all",
        "Both are x and y are equal in value only",
        "Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
      answer: "The local element",
      options: [
        "The local element",
        "Global variable",
        "The two of the above",
        "None"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "Choose the correct snippet from the following to check if the variable “a” is not equal the “NULL”",
      answer: "if(a!==null)",
      options: [
        "if(a!==null)",
        "if (a!)",
        "if(a!=null)",
        "if(a!null)"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "The “function” and ” var” are known as",
      answer: "Declaration statements",
      options: [
        "Keywords",
        "Data types",
        "Prototypes",
        "Declaration statements"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "Suppose we have a text “human” that we want to convert into string without using the “new” operator. Which is the correct way from the following to do so",
      answer: "Both human.toString() and String(human)",
      options: [
        "String newvariable=”human”",
        "String(human)",
        "toString()",
        "Both human.toString() and String(human)"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "In JavaScript, what will be used for calling the function definition expression",
      answer: "Function literal",
      options: [
        "Function literal",
        "Function calling",
        "Function prototype",
        "Function declaration"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "Which of the following one is the property of the primary expression",
      answer: "stand-alone expressions",
      options: [
        "contains variable references alone",
        "Contains only keywords",
        "basic expressions containing all necessary functions",
        "stand-alone expressions"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "Which one of the following is used for the calling a function or a method in the JavaScript",
      answer: "Invocation expression",
      options: [
        "Invocation expression",
        "Functional expression",
        "Property Access Expression",
        "Primary expression"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do",
      answer: "Ignores the statements",
      options: [
        "Throws an error",
        "Prompts to complete the statement",
        "Shows a warning",
        "Ignores the statements"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "The “new Point(3,2)”, is a kind of _______ expression",
      answer: "Object Creation Expression",
      options: [
        "Invocation Expression",
        "Primary Expression",
        "Object Creation Expression",
        "Constructor Calling Expression"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "Which one of the following operator is used to check weather a specific property exists or not",
      answer: "in",
      options: [
        "in",
        "exist",
        "Exists",
        "within"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "What if we define a “for” loop and it removes one of the properties that has not yet been enumerated?",
      answer: "That specific property will not be enumerated",
      options: [
        "The loop will not run at all",
        "The removed property will be stored in a cache",
        "That property will be enumerated",
        "That specific property will not be enumerated"
      ]
    }
  ];
  